<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SubtitleCollection>
  <Subtitles>
    <Subtitle name="Room1Sub1">
      <voiceLine>Good evening 'Contestant'. Had a good nights rest? I hope you did. Because YOU have been chosen as contestant for my little show. Now if you could just walk through the door and into the next room. Then we can start preparing you for the challenges ahead.</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="Room1Sub2">
      <voiceLine>Are you in a rush 'Contestant'? I'm glad to see that. The audience has been waiting for quite a while.</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="Room2Sub1">
      <voiceLine>Now if you could just make it to the other side of the room please. Oh... and do excuse the rubble lying about. You see... this place is not quite finished yet. We are still lacking some finishing touches. But we really couldn't delay the show anymore. That wouldn't be fair to our long waiting audience.</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="Room2Sub2">
      <voiceLine>Oh... You will have to crawl under here... There was supposed to be a door but the production team misread my plans.</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="Room3Sub1">
      <voiceLine>Do you like music 'Contestant'? I do. And you see I have this little habbit of making my contestants record a piece of music just before they enter the show. You know. To have something to remember you by.</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="Room3Sub2">
      <voiceLine>That's a fine piece of music 'Contestant'. Now let's not make the audience wait any longer. Let's go onwards to the show.</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="Level0Idle1">
      <voiceLine>What is it 'Contestent'? Feeling a bit groggy prehaps? It might be the anesthesia. Uhmm... while you recover I'll just play a commercial for the audience.</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub8AN">
      <voiceLine>Humming</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub9">
      <voiceLine>Finally</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub10">
      <voiceLine>Very good. Looks like your legs are working, but we gotta make sure. Jump a couple of times</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub11">
      <voiceLine>Excellent.... Now again</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub12">
      <voiceLine>And again.....</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub13">
      <voiceLine>Again.....</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub14">
      <voiceLine>Just do it 3 more times</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    	  <Subtitle name="T0Sub15">
		  <voiceLine>That's splendid. Your legs seems to be working phenomenally well</voiceLine>
	  </Subtitle>
    	  <Subtitle name="T0Sub16">
		  <voiceLine>Can you guess what to do here?</voiceLine>
	  </Subtitle>
    	  <Subtitle name="T0Sub17">
		  <voiceLine>Watch your head</voiceLine>
	  </Subtitle>
    	  <Subtitle name="T0Sub18">
		  <voiceLine>The production team messed up. We should've had a door here. Instead we got a misplaced wall, just crawl under it</voiceLine>
	  </Subtitle>
    	  <Subtitle name="T0Sub19">
		  <voiceLine>It won't fall on you. I promise</voiceLine>
	  </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub20">
      <voiceLine>You see that button? Your'e gonna see a lot of those. Now press it!</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
      <Subtitle name="T0Sub21">
      <voiceLine>It's locked</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
      <Subtitle name="T0Sub22">
      <voiceLine>You hear that?Sounds like it's locked</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub23">
      <voiceLine>Oh, i thik it's budging.... No it's just my imagination</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub24">
      <voiceLine>Locked</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
      <Subtitle name="T0Sub25">
      <voiceLine>You fiiiiiiinaly figured it out. Well done</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
      <Subtitle name="T0Sub26">
      <voiceLine>I told you so</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub27">
      <voiceLine>Doors normally open if you press 'em, bu sometimes there is a button. This was one of those</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub28">
      <voiceLine>Now go through the door and oooon to the shooooow</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub29">
      <voiceLine>No. No. No. Wrong way. Turn around</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
    <Subtitle name="T0Sub30">
      <voiceLine>What are you DOING?</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
      <Subtitle name="T0Sub31">
      <voiceLine>Alright, since you apparently don't think you're ready, lets take it from the top (sigh)</voiceLine>
    </Subtitle>
  </Subtitles>
</SubtitleCollection>